Guide to the James Beard Foundation Archive 1939-2008 (bulk 1990-2008) MSS.214
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Chefs
  - Gossett, Della, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Gossman, Hans-Trevor, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Goto, Keitaro, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Gottlieb, Dave, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Gottwald, Mark, 1994-1996 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Gould, Mark, 1994-1996 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Gouteyron, Eric, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Gracioni, Cesare, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Gragg, Don, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Graham, Geralyn Delaney, undated (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Graham, James, 1994-1998 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Graham, Kevin, 1990-2005 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Graham, Mark, 2002-2004 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Grahm, Randall, 1989-1998 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Grammatico, Maria, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Grandon, Charles, 1993-1997 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Grangien, Laurent, 1992-2002 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Grant, William, 1996-2000 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Grapes, Colleen, 2001-2005 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Gras, Laurent (Peacock Alley), 1997-2003 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Grassini, Micro, 2001-2004 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Grausman, Richard, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Gray, Michael, undated (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Gray, Todd, 1999-2005 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Graziano, Antonio, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Greaves, Ellen, 1995-1998 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Greenspan, Eric, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Greenspan, Dorie, 1991-2003 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Greenwood, Carole Wagner, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Greenwood, William, 1987-1994 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Greoire, Stephane, 2000-2004 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Grenet, Xavier, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Gresh, Rick, 1996-2001 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - Gresham, Suzette, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Grgich, Mike, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Grgich, Violet, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Grieveson, Koren, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Griffin, Sean, undated (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Grimes, Paul, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Grisanti, Alex, 1996-2001 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Grinker, Josh, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Groban, Reed S., 1992-1998 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Groff, Betty, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Gross, Christopher, 1991-2000 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Grosse, John, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Groveman, Jon, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Groveman, Lauren (1 of 2), 1994-2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Groveman, Lauren (2 of 2), 1991-2003 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Grvppo Ristoratori Italiani, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Guaitonlini, Elio, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Guanga, George, 1995-2003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Guard, Troy, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Guarnaschelli, Alexandra, 2001-2005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Guas, David, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Guay, Thomas, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Gubbins, Amiko, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Guerard, Michel, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Guerithault, Vincent, 1986-1994 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Guerrera, Domanie, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Guiffrida, Matthew, 2005-2008 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Gugliemelli, Tony, 2000-2003 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Guia, Carlos, 2002-2004 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Guiliano, Marcus, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Guillermo, Pernot, 2004-2008 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Guilja, Douglas, 1997-2000 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Guillas, Bernard, 1989-2004 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Gulli, Gerry, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Guillory, Donald, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Guillotin, Pascal, 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Gunyan, Michael, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Gupta, Sameer, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Gustafsson, P.G., 1990-1997 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Gutenbrunner, Kurt, 1997-2003 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Guthrie, William, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Gutierrez, Ignacio, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Gutierrez, Jose, 1989-2003 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Gutow, Tom, 1994-2005 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Gyermek, Laszlo, 1986-1992 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Haas, Robbin, 1994-2000 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Haas, Thomas, 1999-2004 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Habashi, Ehab, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Haddad, Philippe, 1989-1999 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Hadjiparaskevas, Harry (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Haegele, Scott, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Haeger, Kevin, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Hage, Sharon, undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Hageman, Wade, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Hagenbart, Melissa Murphy, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Haifley, Justin, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Haight, Marcus, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Hafner, Joseph, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Haimowitz, Michael, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Halberg, Rick, 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Hale, Rex, 1990-1997 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Hall, Eric, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Hall, Todd, 1991-1997 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Halligan, John, 1992-2002 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Halpert, Fred, 1993-1996 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Halston, Andre, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Hamann, Martin, 1997-2005 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Hambrecht, Eric, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Hamersley, Gordon, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Hamilton, Gabrielle, 1999-2005 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Hamilton, Jim/Mark Miller, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Hamilton, Richard, 1998-2008 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Hanahan, James, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Hancey, Don, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Handke, Hartmut, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Handy, John T., 2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Hannan, Patrick, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Hansen, Gary, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Hanson, Lee, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Hanson, Steve, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Harary, Nicholas, 2001-2005 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Hara, Eric, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Hardel, Fabrice, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Harding, Alan, 1992-2006 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Hardy, Ryan, 1993-2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Hardy, Sean, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Harings, John, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Harkins, Tom, 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Harney, Michael, 1990-1996 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Harootunian, Jonathan, 1990-1996 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Harraseeket Inn/Theda Lyden and Nathan Beriau, 1994-2005 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Harrell, Linda, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Harris, Glen, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Harris, Henry, 1996-1998 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Harris, John, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Harris, Thomas, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Harris, Valentina, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Harrison, Clifford, 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Hart, Nancy, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Hartman, Craig, 1992-2003 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Harvest (Tami Lax and Justin Carlisle), 2006 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Harvey, Peter D., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Hastings, Christopher, 1997-2006 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Haugen, Mark, 1988-2004 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Haurey, James, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Haverkock, Guido, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Haverty, Dan, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Havlis, John, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Hawaiian Vintage Chocolate Organization, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Hawksworth, David, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Haxaire, Thierry, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Hayashi, Remi, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Hayden, David, undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Hayden, Gerry, 1993-2004 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Hayot, Roger, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Hayward, Sam, 1992-2004 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Haywood, Jim and Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Hazen, Sam, 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Healy, Derek, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Healy, Patrick, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Heap, Bradford, 1992-1996 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Hearon, Reed, 1993-1999 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Hebben, Richard, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Heffernan, Kerry, 1991-1996 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Hefter, Lee (Spago), 1999 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Heidel, Don, 1991-1994 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Heierling, Martin, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Heiland, Gunther, 1995-1998 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Hellrigl, Andreas, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Helm, Maria, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Helm, Scott, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Helmer, Howard, undated (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Helstrom, Robert, 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Henlemann, Thomas, 1992-1999 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Henney, Michael, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Henriroux, Patrick, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Henry, Mark, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Henry, Ramon S., undated (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Hensley, Johndavid, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Herbeck, Rene, 1991-1997 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Herbitscheck, Erich, undated (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Herme, Pierre, 1995-2005 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Hernandez, Carmen/Marian Ramirez, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Hernandez, Marisoll, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Hernandez, Simon, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Herold, Martin, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Herrick, Colleen, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Herschman, Michael, 1997-2005 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Hewitt, Jean, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Hewson, Andrew, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Hewson, Doug, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Hewey, Corey, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Hibbs, Mark, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Hickey, Kevin, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Hicks, Jason, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Higgins, Greg, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Higgins, John, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Higuchi, Naohiro, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Hill, Alan, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Hill, Barbara, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Hill, Bruce, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Hill, Gregory, 1994-1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Hill, Jon, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Hillyard, Josh, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Hinds, Walter, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Hines, Maria L., 2001-2006 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Hirabayashi, Wayne, 1996-2002 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Hirogoyen, Gerald, 1991-2002 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Hirose, Akira, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Hirsch, George, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Hirschberg, Michael, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Hiscock, Ken, undated (Box 20, Folder 30a)
  - Hitchins, Brenda, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 30b)
  - Hnilo, Ken, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Ho, Stanton, 1994-2006 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Hodge, William, 1990-1997 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Hodgins, Vincent, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Hoefler, Peter, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Hoffa, Jeffrey, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Hoffman, Adrian, undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Hoffman, Peter, 1991-2003 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Hoffman, Stephanie, undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Hofminster, Raymond, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Hogan, John, 1994-1999 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Hogan, Todd, 1994-2000 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Hoge, James, undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Hoguet, Diana, 1985-1992 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Holben, David, 1994-2006 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Holder, Geoffrey, 1984-1992 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Holland, Susan, undated (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Holleman, Gary Bruce, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Holley, Mark, 2001-2004 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Holley, Robert, undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Hollis, Chris, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Hollocou, Richard, undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Holmes, Mike, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Homquist, Zane; Raymond Lammers; D.W. Scheidell, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Holzberg, Marty, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Hom, Ken, 1984-1991 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Hoobler, Michael, 1997-2004 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Hood, Shields, 1974-1996 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Hooper, Jim, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Hopkins, Gordon, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Hopkins, Linton, undated (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Hopper, Mark, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Horner, Thomas, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Hosack, Mark, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Hosmer, Bart, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Hotel Del Cornado, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Houle, Danforth, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Houlihan, Walter, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - House of Blues, 1993-1996 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Hover, Daniel, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Hovis, Gene, 1987-2004 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Howard, Cameron, 1993-1997 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Howard, Josefina, 1988-1995 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Howard, Martin, 1993-1999 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Howard, Philip, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Howe, Rosemary, 1989-1997 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Howell, Michael, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Howell, Scott, 1993-2001 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Howie, John, 1997-2002 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Hoyland, Scott, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Hsu, En-Ming, undated (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Hubert, Chris, 1993-2002 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Hudock, James, 1994-1998 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Huff, Joel, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Hughes, Alan Patricio, 1995-2003 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Hulin, Guy, 2001-2004 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Hulse, Todd, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Humm, Daniel, 2000-2004 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Humphries, Todd, 1993-1999 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Hunnel, Scott, 1988-1996 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - Hunter, Angela, undated (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - Hurapan, Taweewat, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - Hurley, Bob, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - Hurley, Tom, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - Hurtado, Jose, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Husbards, Andy, 1995-2005 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - Hustod, Stephen, 1984-1992 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - Hutchins, Brian, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  - Hurapan, Dejathana, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Hutchings, Michael, 1984-1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Hutchinson, Abigail, 2004-2006 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Hutnik, Dano, 1985-2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Hutson, Cindy, 1999-2004 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Huyke, Giovanna, 1986-1992 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Huynh, Michael, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Hvid, Jeff, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Hyman, Lee, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Iaccarino Family, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Iacovelli, Jean-Claude, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Iacoviello, Franco, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Iacovone, Robert, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Ibanez, Bernard, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Ibarra, Bernard, 1998-2002 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Ida, Jean, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Idaho Potato Commission, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Idone, Christopher, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Ifshin, Noelle, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Iijima, Mika, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Illy, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Imbrolio, John, 1997-2002 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Inahara, Jeffrey, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Ingber, Sandy, 1999-2005 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Ingenito, Paul, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Ingram, Shane, 1999-2002 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Insingo, Francesco, 1965-1999 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Culinary Education, 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Iocco, Marisa, 1994-2001 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Ireland, Peter, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Irizar, Luis, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Isaac, Eric, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Ishii, Jimmy, 1997-2002 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Islam, Mohammad, 1994-2004 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Israel, Christopher, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Ithurritze, Christophe, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Iuzzini, Johnny, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Izaguirre, Inaki, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Jackson, Bill, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Jackson, Daniel, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Jackson, Elizabeth Nicolas, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Jackson, Jeff, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Jackson, Patti, 2002-2006 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Jackson, Ryan, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Jacobs, Jake, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Jacobs, Todd, 1991-1998 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Jacobson, Morgen, 1992-1999 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Jacquet, Philippe, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Jallepalli-Reiss, Raji, 2001-2003 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Jallepalli, Raji, 1991-2002 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Jamain, Dominique, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - James, Jeff, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - James, Marvin, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - James, Michael, 1998-2002 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - James, Miles, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - James, Stephen, undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Jamison, Michael, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Jammet, Andre, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Japngie, Linda, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Jarrett, Kirstin and Steven, 1994-1998 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Jarvis, David, 1989-1994 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Jasinki, Jennifer, 2002-2004 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Jaulin, Etienne, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Jean-Louis, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Jean, Michel, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Jean, Robert, 2002-2007 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Jeanty, Philippe, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Jefferds, Gary, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Jenkins, Paul, undated (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Jenkins, Sara, 1998-2005 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Jenkins, Sara, 1998-2005 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - Jennings, Bret, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Jensen, Erling, 1996-2005 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - Jensen, Mark, 1996-2000 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - Jermonti, Pierino, 1998-2006 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - Jessick, Rodney, 1998-2002 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - Jochum, Konrad, undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - John, Thomas, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Johnson, Bruce, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - Johnson, Carol, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - Johnson, Chris, undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - Johnson, David, 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Johnson, Grant, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - Johnson, John, 1995-2004 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Johnson, Kenneth, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - Johnson, Scott, undated (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - Johnson, Steve, undated (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - Johnson, Wayne, 1996-2003 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - Johnsson, Roger, 2003-2005 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - Johnsten, Brian, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - Johnston, Larry, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Joho, Jean, 1989-2000 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Jolis, Jennifer, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Joly, Daniel, 1981-2006 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Jones, Chris, 1993-1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Jones, David, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Evan, 1989-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Gary, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Kimball, 1999-2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Lee, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jonilonis, Jason, 1994-1997 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Jorand, Alain, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Jordan, Anthony, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Jordan, Michael and Wenday, 1999-2003 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Jordan, Michele Anna, 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Joseph, Toby, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Josselin, Jean-Marie, 1991-2005 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Joseph, Toby, 2000-2005 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Joudeh, Saleh, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Jovic, Nicola, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Juary, Victor, 1997-2001 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Juran, Kenneth, 1993-1997 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Jurich, Todd, 1991-2006 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Kadish, Ephraim, 1993-1998 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Kadosh, Shalom, 1992-2000 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Kagawa, Hitoshi, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Kahan, Paul, 1997-2002 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Kahn, Daniel, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Kalajian, Michael, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Kaliff, William, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Kalman, Bruce, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Kalt, Stephen, 1994-2002 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Kamnitzer, Erasmo "Razz", 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Kanfer, Scooter, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Kang, Michael, 1987-1999 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Kang, Yujean, 1992-1998 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Kangas, Rick, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Kaniger, Dennis, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Kaplan, Nicole, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Kaplan, Marlin, 1999-2005 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Kaplan, Roger, 1993-1996 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Kappes, Stefan, undated (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Karamardian, Zov, 1994-2005 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Karasz, Andrew, 2002-2006 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Karatassos, Pano, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Karmel, Elizabeth, 2002-2007 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Karp, Matthew, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Karousos, George, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Karousos, Theodore, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Katz, Douglas, 1998-2004 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Katz, Elizabeth, undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Katzl, Donna, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Kaufelt, Robert, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Kaufman, Chrysa, 1994-1997 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Kaufmann, Hans, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Kawachi, Tod Michael, 1996-1998 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Kaytmay, Ugur, undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Keegan, Tim, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Kaysen, Gavin, 2003-2006 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Keane, Douglas, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Kearney, Anne, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Keating, Tim, 1992-2003 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Keatley, Chris and Jonathan Pratt, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Keck, Katy, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Keegan, Joseph, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Kedem, Ezra, undated (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Keff, Christine, 1993-2007 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Keh, David, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Keller, Boris, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Keller, Cynthia and Michel, 1992-2004 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Keller, Duane, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Keller, Hubert, 1992-1998 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Keller, Joseph, 1980-2006 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Keller, Loretta, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Keller, Karen, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Keller, Thomas, 1987-2006 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Kelley, Brad, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Kelley, Michael, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Kelley, Tim, 1994-2002 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Kelly, Christian, 2002-2005 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Kelly, Christina, 1999-2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Kelly, Melissa, 1996-2004 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Kelly, Patricia, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Kelly, Peter, 1983-2002 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Kelly, Sean, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Kennan, Helene, 1999-2003 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Kennard, Stephen, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy, Billy, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy-Tilyou, Lynn, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Kenney, Matthew, 1990-2002 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Kestenboum, Yaron, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Keyser, Paul, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Khadija El Abbadi, Lala, 2002-2006 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Khanloo, Hossein, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Khanna, Vikas, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Khorshidi, Reza, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Khunn, Sottha, 1993-1998 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Kidd, Scott, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Kidder, Chris and Kimberly Sklar, 2005-2006 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Kido, Sherrie, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Kieffer, Frederic, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Kiely, Charles, 1994-2000 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Kiffin, Mark, 1995-2003 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Kikuchi, Koh, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Killeen, Johanne, 1986-1999 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Kim, Alexander, 1988-1997 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Kim, Dan, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Kim, Onjin, 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Kimmel, Stephanie Pearl, 1997-2004 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Kimura, Shinji, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Kimpton, Bill, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Kinch, David, 1996-2004 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Kinchela, Nancy, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Kindel, Peter, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - King, Earl, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - King, Kathleen, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - King, Monique and Paul Rosenbluh, 2002-2005 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - King, William, 2002-2005 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Kingsbury, Seth, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Kinkead, Robert, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Kinney, Pat, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 42)